http://www.crystalimagephoto.com/privacy-policy.html

Return Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Crystal Image Photography collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.crystalimagephoto.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Crystal Image Photography.Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How we use collected informationCrystal Image Photography may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:- To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.- To process paymentsWe may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.- To send periodic emailsWe may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.How we protect your informationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.Sharing your personal informationWe do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identifiable information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identifying information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.Third party websitesUsers may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.Changes to this privacy policyCrystal Image Photography has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:Crystal Image Photographywww.crystalimagephoto.com200 North Street, Farmville, VA 23901434-610-8917cip4you@gmail.comThis document was last updated on January 01, 2020
What Our Clients Are Saying
Crystal was a great photographer for our wedding! She's definitely LGBT friendly and has some cool rainbow umbrellas to use as props in your pictures - if that's your style. Our friends and family were all very impressed with the number of photos she took and shared with us - and they're all great shots! We would absolutely recommend her to others. - Kelsey and Shannon - Baltimore, MarylandWhen I got engaged, I knew who I wanted to take our engagement pictures and also photograph our wedding. I contacted Crystal and asked her if she would be willing to come to Gettysburg, PA to take our engagement pictures and she was more than happy to drive 4 1/2 hours to our farm to capture my "farmer fiancé" and I in the cornfield, in our sunflower field and on our combine. On the day she drove up to take our pictures, it was a really hot and humid August day. She walked around the farm with us snapping pictures and was willing to do whatever we wanted. She did an amazing job capturing who we were and was patient with us when we changed outfits. We also hired Crystal to also photograph our wedding the following September. We filled out a questionnaire beforehand so she knew exactly what kinds of pictures we were wanting her to take. A few days before our wedding, she called and made sure everything was on schedule and letting us know what time we would expect her to arrive at the wedding. My fiancé and I did a "First Look" before the wedding and Crystal was so professional and everything went so smoothly. I can't begin to say how satisfied we are with our wedding pictures!! They were absolutely beautiful! She took pictures of all the little detailed things! I would highly recommend Crystal if you are looking for a photographer! - Chrissy and Dave - Gettysburg, PARead more reviews here.
Contact Us
Home
Meet Crystal
Galleries
Weddings
Engagement
H.S. Seniors
Pricing
